<fomod>
  <Name>Milk Mod Economy</Name>
  <Version>19-09-2017</Version>
  <Author>Ed86</Author>
  <Website>http://www.loverslab.com/files/file/1382-milk-mod-economy/</Website>
  <Description>
  
Dev change log:

	v 19-09-2017
ported sksesless rnd script from SSE
added toggle to disable armor stripping

	v 23-08-2017
debuffs system overhaul
removed 50 spells with fixed values, added 2 spells with dynamic values,
so for every milk character has, stats will be reduced by 1, so if your cow girl wonders outside of barn unprepared, she better be prepared for consequences and bad end?
on the buff side you get (MilkMax-MilkCnount)*BreastsSize_Node bonus carry weight, probably a huge boost, that is if you'll be able to keep breasts well milked
added breasts debuff, this one reduces stats depending on breast size*weight, which should be something like (1..9)*(1..2)

	v 03-08-2017
removed sexlaborgasm toggle
removed breasfeeding toggle
hidden debug content under debug toggle

	v 02-08-2017
changed:
automatic cuirass milking to happen when breasts 75% full instead of 1 milk
living armors will no longer feed lactacid if actor have milk

	v 30-07-2017
moved DDI vibrate event hook to DDI plug-in script

	v 28-07-2017
fixed male checks in scripts for male milking

	v 27-07-2017
fixed? ineed giving "error" when not installed in mod checks(shouldn't affect anything, if your skyrim broken it wont fix it)
fixed left breast milk leak art
removed gender checks for malemaids dialogues(except futa creation)
doubled cuirass weight to 2/4(normal/futa)
halved bell/horns weight to 0.5
increased 4/6/8 tits armor weight to 12.5, 25, 50
reduced tits armor cost from "alot" to 0, say "NO" to second hand titties sales!

	v 24-07-2017
fix milkslaves 10 ->100
added mcm option(under debug) to toggle malemaids

	v 21-07-2017
fix for DD suits unequipp

	v 17-07-2017
increased maid slave count to 100, requires mod reset
added ability to milk males, they should be female when you make them milk maid
reduced pain from hand milking, milking will stop, before getting exhaustion debuff
milkmaid with well-milked buff can no longer be milked(less than 40% max milk)
added armor stripping when player has 4/8/12 milk
updated playeralias script, merged sl orgasm and slso functions
fixed incorrect milktick per hour in mcm


	v 30-06-2017
succubus milk, turns player into succubus:
added event for angrim aprentice event, dont remember if AA actually support this
added event for deadly drain
added forced turn into PSQ succubus

hidden most scripts in CK
changed most scipts names
removed properties from most scripts
set a base for porting mod variables\ messages into jsons

	v 27-06-2017
dialogue scripts overhaul

 </Description>
</fomod>