<fomod>
  <Name>Milk Mod Economy</Name>
  <Version>08-04-2018</Version>
  <Author>Ed86</Author>
  <Website>https://www.patreon.com/Ed86</Website>
  <Description>
  
Dialogue trade:
*milk sold through dialogues is done through economy script, thus affecting economy and can yield more income 

Khajiits merchants:
-buy all milk
-trade Lactacid for milk
Orc merchants(wise woman):
-buy normal and race milk
Inns:
-buy race milk
alchemists: 					
-buy ww/vampire/succubus milk
-buy cum/semen
-sell Lactacid for 100g/bottle
-sell Breast enlargement potion for 1000g
Fences:
-buy all milk
Farmers:
-buy normal milk
-sell Lactacid for 100g/bottle


Milk Pump locations:
DawnStar
Falkreath
Markarth
 - outside of dibella's temple
Orc strongholds (Features bound milkpumps, they wont let you(player) get out until you are milked dry)
Riften
 - outside of mara's temple
 - Shor's stone
Solitude
 - Dragon's bridge
 - Morthal
Whiterun
 - behind the blacksmith
 - Riverwood
 - Rorikstead
Windhelm
 - near the blacksmith
 - Winterhold
Caravan
 - Ivarstead

Placing your own Milk Pumps:
You can place Milk Pump anywhere you want, they might even affect economy.
a)	Using console:
	1) help milk
	2) get id of FURN Milk Pump
	3) player.placeatme id from above
	4) use [url=http://www.nexusmods.com/skyrim/mods/60910/]Jaxonz Positioner[/url] to adjust position

b)	Using Campire mod to craft and place milkpumps
  
  
Dev change log:

	v 08-04-2018
remembered to upload v 26-03-2018

	v 26-03-2018
added pregnancy check through keywords for EC/ES/ED
finally added what you all were waiting for, translation files for spells configuration page

	v 21-03-2018
fixed Setunconscious() disabling player milking controls

	v 19-03-2018
fixed armor not stripping when breast are full
fixed incorrect futacum output after milking 

	v 17-03-2018-hf
prevent lactacid activation to become milkmaid in combat and on mount
fix for storymaker %text
fix legacy mods that have no support for "MilkBarrel"
added Setunconscious() to actors during mobile milking/ 1st lactacid use to avoid npcs moving while animating

	v 17-03-2018
fixed milking not properly ending for actors with armors that cant be stripped(and probably naked)
changed all(used to be only orc camps) bound milkpumps to produce only half milk for free lactacid
changed cum addition to milked actor, rather than player
added ability for modders to add milk to "MilkBarrel" objectreference after milking rather than actor

	v 12-03-2018
added x10 lactacid trade dialogues for alchemists and farmers
added option to disable scripts check if mod fails to start(ohh i'll probably gonna regret this)

	v 09-03-2018
fixed broken dynamic storyteller script("name's breasts" errors etc )
changed milk generation conditions. To increase milk production you need to either drink lactacid or be pregnant and not have full breasts, milking and animations with "Breast" tag will also increase milk production
you may use "MaidLevel Progression Affects MilkGen" toggle to increase production rate and slow down its drop rate when not pregnant or not on lactacid
added condition to prevent armor(slot 32) stripping if it has sexlabnostrip keyword, that should probably fix issues with some DD items

	v 18-02-2018
fixed mcm maid debug page

	v 15-02-2018
added toggle to disable Exhaustion Debuff
reduced Exhaustion Debuff strength 90%->50%
reached mcm limit, time to add another mcm yay!

	v 14-02-2018
added toggle to disable cum bottles production
added toggle to disable animations play during mobile milking
added SSE scaling patch for those who have ported mod to SSE, so body scaling works on old Netimmerse

	v 15-01-2018
added description of fuckmachine toggle
added toggle to disable 40% milk fullness requirement for mobile milking


 </Description>
</fomod>