<fomod>
  <Name>Milk Mod Economy</Name>
  <Version>30-07-2017</Version>
  <Author>Ed86</Author>
  <Website>http://www.loverslab.com/files/file/1382-milk-mod-economy/</Website>
  <Description>
  
Dev change log:

	v 30-07-2017
moved DDI vibrate event hook to DDI plug-in script

	v 28-07-2017
fixed male checks in scripts for male milking

	v 27-07-2017
fixed? ineed giving "error" when not installed in mod checks(shouldn't affect anything, if your skyrim broken it wont fix it)
fixed left breast milk leak art
removed gender checks for malemaids dialogues(except futa creation)
doubled cuirass weight to 2/4(normal/futa)
halved bell/horns weight to 0.5
increased 4/6/8 tits armor weight to 12.5, 25, 50
reduced tits armor cost from "alot" to 0, say "NO" to second hand titties sales!

	v 24-07-2017
fix milkslaves 10 ->100
added mcm option(under debug) to toggle malemaids

	v 21-07-2017
fix for DD suits unequipp

	v 17-07-2017
increased maid slave count to 100, requires mod reset
added ability to milk males, they should be female when you make them milk maid
reduced pain from hand milking, milking will stop, before getting exhaustion debuff
milkmaid with well-milked buff can no longer be milked(less than 40% max milk)
added armor stripping when player has 4/8/12 milk
updated playeralias script, merged sl orgasm and slso functions
fixed incorrect milktick per hour in mcm


	v 30-06-2017
succubus milk, turns player into succubus:
added event for angrim aprentice event, dont remember if AA actually support this
added event for deadly drain
added forced turn into PSQ succubus

hidden most scripts in CK
changed most scipts names
removed properties from most scripts
set a base for porting mod variables\ messages into jsons

	v 27-06-2017
dialogue scripts overhaul

	v 31-05-2017
fix? for npcs to prevent them from trying to milk them-self during update while player is far away thus causing errors in log

	v 26-05-2017
fix for infinite milkgen increase with milklevelcap
changed maid progression option to affect milkgen reduction

	v 18-05-2017
pumps collision fix

	v 27-04-2017
RND overhaul, may need cleansave
SLSO support

	v 20-02-2017
changed sos script to use jsons, you can manually add sos addons you dont want to be recognized as penis

	v 19-01-2017
fix for broken economy by 14-01-2017, requires mod variables reset

	v 14-01-2017
some edits to prevent endless script loops if mod is broken but somehow still manages to start 
fix for EC/ES animations

 </Description>
</fomod>